# ZUNAIRA ASIF

# FRONTEND DEVELOPER

#### CONTACT

+

+92 303 4774200



zunairaa.dev@gmail.com



Sahiwal, Pakistan







#### SKILLS

HTML

React JS

CSS

Next JS

JavaScript

Shopify

TypeScript

React Native

Tailwind CSS

REST APIs

Github

EDUCATION

2018-2022

#### **BS** (Computer Science)

The University of Lahore, Lahore CGPA - 3.11

2016-2018

## Intermediate

Divisional Public School and Inter College (DPS), Sahiwal

# LANGUAGES

English



Urdu

#### ABOUT

I'm a skilled Frontend Developer specializing in React.js, Next.js, Shopify and React Native. Passionate and motivated person that focus on delivering scalable, responsive and user-friendly applications by utilizing modern techniques and best practices. Dedicated to constantly learning and face complex challenges to enhance my skills for both personal as well as professional growth.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### **Freelance Developer**

01/2024 - Present

#### **MLPB Armory**

https://dev.mlpbarmory.com/

- A blockchain project built on Next.js
- Built minting portal and email templates.
- Mostly worked on responsiveness issues and other bugs.

#### **Finarch**

https://finarch.co/

- · An architect website developed using React.js
- Used MUI for responsive and flexible design.
- Worked with integrating API's.

#### **Ghoomo Phiroo Pakistan**

https://gpp.codeminer.co/

- Developed an admin panel for a Travel Agency using React.js
- Integrated API's.

#### AltCode Labs

10/2022 - 12/2023

## **AltCode Labs**

https://www.altcodelabs.com/

- Developed company's website in Next.js
- Worked with MUI for flexible design.
- Implemented 3D animations using Framer motion and Sketchfab.

#### **Fitcy Health**

https://fitcyhealth.com/

- Fitcy health is a **React.js** Web App serves as Mental Health Care platform.
- Implemented all API's.
- Fixed many UI bugs using Grommet library.